Guide to the Syria Collection of photographs AD.MC.036
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Marie Rose Krikorian Series (Box 5, Box 9, Box 1)
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian and a man wearing kimonos., Circa 1965-1970; ref705; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Women; Men; Regional/National Dress; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Facial Hair; Clocks/Watches; Furnishings
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian with three small children sitting in a window sill., 1949; ref706; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 x 7 cm (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Women; Children; Boys; Girls; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of two women and a man walking down stairs., 1966; ref707; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Men; Women; Outdoors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; French Writing
  - A group portrait of a woman in floral dress holding a baby., Circa 1940-1970; ref708; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 3.2 cm (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Women; Children; Outdoors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of several people near a picnic blanket, including Marie (far left) and Jareh Krikorian (center)., Circa 1940-1950; ref709; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6 cm (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Women; Men; Picnic; Photographic Prints; Syria; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Water; Food; Gatherings
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian sitting outside with Jareh Krikorian., 1948; ref710; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 6.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Men; Women; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Nice, France; French Writing
  - A group portrait of three women, a man, and a young boy next to a river., Circa 1940-1950; ref711; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Rivers; Men; Women; Picnic; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Food; Gatherings; Boys; Children
  - A group portrait of a woman and a man at a table with Marie Krikorian (far left)., Circa 1940-1965; ref712; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 6.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Men; Women; Food; Drinks/Beverages; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Restaurants/bars
  - Berengaria Hotel, Cyprus., Circa 1940-1970; ref713; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.3 x 6.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Hotels; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Prodromos, Cyprus
  - A group portrait of two young boys in overalls on a platform., Circa 1940-1970; ref714; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 6.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Boys; Children; Outdoors; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of young boy and a baby smiling., Circa 1940-1970; ref715; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 6.1 cm (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of several people near a body of water., Circa 1940-1950; ref716; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Water; Rivers; Men; Women; Picnic; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Gatherings; Food
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian holding two young boys., Circa 1940-1960; ref717; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 6.1 cm (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Women; Children; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Boys
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian holding two young boys (linked ref 717)., Circa 1940-1960; ref718; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 6.1 cm (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Women; Children; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boys
  - A portrait of a baby smiling., 1946; ref719; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 6 cm (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; French Writing; Syria; Children
  - A portrait of a baby in its cradle (linked ref 719)., 1946; ref720; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 6 cm (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria; French Writing; Children
  - A studio envelope for Photo Boyadjian., Circa 1940-1970; ref721; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 x 7.1 cm (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Damascus, Syria; Advertisements; Art; Women; French Writing; English Writing; Printed Materials
  - A portrait of Jareh Krikorian sitting in a car., Circa 1945-1960; ref722; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 8.8 cm (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Men; Cars/Trucks; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria; Transportation
  - A multigenerational group portrait of several men, women, and children including Marie Rose and Jareh Krikorian (right)., Circa 1945-1960; ref723; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.6 x 8.7 cm (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Men; Children; Boys; Girls
  - A group portrait of a woman with three children sitting in an airplane prop., Circa 1945-1960; ref724; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 8.8 cm (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Airplanes; Boys; Children; Women; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria; Studio Photography; Painted Backdrops; Transportation
  - A group portrait of three women, two men, including Jareh Krikorian, and Marie Rose Krikorian holding a child (left)., Circa 1945-1960; ref725; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.6 x 8.6 cm (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Men; Children; Women; Restaurants/bars; Boys; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Food; Drinks/Beverages; Facial Hair; Jewelry
  - A studio portrait of a young child wearing a sweater., Circa 1945-1960; ref726; Studio Georges Derzi, Press Photography Department, Salhieh, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 13.2 x 8.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Boys; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria; Children; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a baby in a white dress., Circa 1940-1970; ref727; Studio Dikran, Damascus, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 13.5 x 8.2 cm (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Jewelry; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Children
  - A studio portrait of a baby standing on a couch next to a rocking horse (linked ref727)., Circa 1940-1970; ref728; Studio Dikran, Damascus, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 13.4 x 8.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Toys; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Children
  - A postcard of a beach in France from Marie Rose and Jareh Krikorian., 21 November 1948; ref729; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.1 x 9.1 cm (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Nice, France; Streets/Roads; Palm Trees; Water; Beaches; Postcards; Gelatin Silver Prints; French Writing; Landscapes; Signatures
  - A postcard of The Transfiguration of Raphael written to Marie Rose Krikorian., 1955; ref730; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.2 x 10.2 cm (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Paintings; Postcards; Men; French Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria; Art; Group Portraits; Signatures
  - A group portrait of several people around a dinner table, while a man dangles food in front of his face., Circa 1960-1970; ref731; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Food; Gatherings; Boys; Girls; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of several young adults around a dinner table doing bunny ears., Circa 1960-1970; ref732; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Children; Boys; Girls; Gatherings; Food; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of several people crowded near a couch., Circa 1960-1970; ref733; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Boys; Girls; Children; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Gatherings
  - A group portrait of several young adults around a dinner table., Circa 1960-1970; ref734; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Girls; Boys; Children; Food; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gatherings; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of a teenage boy dancing with a girl, a child kneels in the background., Circa 1960-1970; ref735; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Boys; Girls; Children; Dancing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria; Gatherings
  - A group portrait of several people passing food around a table., Circa 1960-1970; ref736; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Boys; Girls; Children; Food; Gatherings; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of several people around a table holding tea cups., Circa 1960-1970; ref737; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Girls; Boys; Children; Food; Gatherings; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of four boys laying on the ground with camping supplies., 1966; ref738; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Boys; Lanterns/Lamps; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; French Writing; Children
  - A portrait of a man standing on top of a stone structure., 1966; ref739; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Architecture; Men; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; French Writing
  - A portrait of a person walking under an archway., 1966; ref740; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Architecture; Women; Syria; French Writing; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A mountain landscape., Circa 1960-1970; ref741; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; French Writing
  - A group portrait of two boys looking into a rocky valley., Circa 1960-1970; ref742; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Boys; Children; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; French Writing; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes
  - A group portrait of two boys standing on rock., Circa 1960-1970; ref743; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Mountains/Hills; Boys; Children; Syria; French Writing; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a boy looking out to a village., Circa 1960-1970; ref744; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Buildings; Mountains/Hills; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; French Writing; Maaloula/Maʿlūlā, Syria
  - A group portrait of four boys standing with hiking supplies., Circa 1960-1970; ref745; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Mountains/Hills; Boys; Children; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; French Writing
  - A landscape of a campsite., Circa 1960-1970; ref746; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Tents; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Forest/Woodlands; Men; Syria; Group Portraits; French Writing
  - A campsite surrounded by trees., 1966; ref747; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Group Portraits; Tents; Syria; Forest/Woodlands; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; French Writing
  - A landscape of a village in a rocky valley., Circa 1960-1970; ref748; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Buildings; Landscapes; Syria; French Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mountains/Hills
  - A group portrait of a young man and woman dancing., 1966; ref749; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Women; Men; Dancing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; French Writing; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Signatures
  - A group portrait of two boys in front of tents., Circa 1960-1970; ref750; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Mountains/Hills; Tents; Boys; Outdoors; Children; Syria; French Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Landscapes
  - A group portrait of two boys in a rocky ravine., Circa 1960-1970; ref751; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Outdoors; Men; Photographic Prints; French Writing; Group Portraits; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a boy looking down at the village of Maaloula/Maʿlūlā, Syria., Circa 1960-1970; ref752; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Mountains/Hills; Boys; Children; Buildings; Maaloula/Maʿlūlā, Syria; French Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Landscapes
  - A portrait of a young boy stuck in sand., 1966; ref753; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; French Writing
  - A group portrait of five men near tents., 1966; ref754; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Tents; Men; Boys; Children; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; French Writing
  - A portrait of a man reading in his underwear., 1966; ref755; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 cm x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Books; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; French Writing
  - A portrait of a man wearing boxers at a swimming pool., Circa 1960-1970; ref756; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Swimming; Swimming Pools; Boys; Men; Children; Syria; French Writing; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Signatures
  - The village of Maaloula (Maʿlūlā)., Circa 1960-1970; ref757; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mountains/Hills; Buildings; Maaloula/Maʿlūlā, Syria; Mosques; Photographic Prints; French Writing; Religious Sites
  - A studio envelope featuring Gevaert rollfilm., Circa 1960-1970; ref758; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.2 x 9.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Syria; Advertisements; Cameras; Women; Men; Art; Printed Materials
  - A group portrait of three women including Marie Rose Krikorian, three men and a young girl at a restaurant., Circa 1950-1970; ref759; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.9 x 13 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Women; Men; Girls; Children; Syria; Restaurants/bars; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Drinks/Beverages
  - A group portrait of a Marie Rose Krikorian smoking next to Jareh Krikorian and a young girl., Circa 1950-1970; ref760; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.6 x 12.6 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Girls; Children; Smoking; Cigarettes; Hats; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Drinks/Beverages; Restaurants/bars
  - A group portrait of two women, including Marie Rose Krikorian (right), and two men at a table., Circa 1950-1970; ref761; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.8 x 12.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Restaurants/bars; Syria; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Drinks/Beverages; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait with Jareh Krikorian (left) smoking with another man and Marie Rose Krikorian., Circa 1950-1970; ref762; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.9 x 12.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Smoking; Jewelry; Cigarettes; Restaurants/bars; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Group Portraits; Drinks/Beverages
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose and Jareh Krikorian dancing., Circa 1950-1970; ref763; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.8 x 12.7 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Jewelry; Dancing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria; Gatherings
  - A group portrait of two women, including Marie Rose Krikorian (center), and three men wearing formal clothing at a dinner table., Circa 1950-1970; ref764; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.9 x 12.7 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Restaurants/bars; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria; Drinks/Beverages
  - A portrait of Jareh Krikorian wearing sunglasses in a car., Circa 1950-1970; ref765; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.8 x 11 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Cars/Trucks; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria; Men; Transportation
  - A group portrait of four men in suits, including Jareh Krikorian, and Marie Rose Krikorian in a paisley dress., Circa 1950-1970; ref766; Studio Safar & Vartan, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 12.1 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair
  - A portrait of someone sticking their finger in a woman's mouth., Circa 1940-1970; ref767; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.9 x 13 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Women; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian wearing sunglasses., Circa 1950-1970; ref768; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.1 x 18 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Women; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of four women and three men at a dinner table, including Marie Rose and Jareh Krikorian (left)., Circa 1950-1970; ref769; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.1 x 12.8 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Jewelry; Restaurants/bars; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Fur Garments
  - A group portrait of two women wearing headscarves and a man in a suit., Circa 1950-1970; ref770; Al Douli International Studio, Damascus (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Bags/Purses; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria; Outdoors; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian in a fur coat looking at a man in a suit., Circa 1940-1965; ref771; Studio Mesmar, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 19.5 x 12.1 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Restaurants/bars; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Drinks/Beverages; Fur Garments; Food
  - A group portrait of several people around a dinner table including Marie Rose Krikorian (back left)., Circa 1950-1970; ref772; Photo Quick, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 20.3 x 12.6 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Restaurants/bars; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria; Gatherings; Drinks/Beverages
  - A group portrait of two men, including Jareh Krikorian, and Marie Rose Krikorian around a dinner table., Circa 1950-1970; ref773; Issa Freres, Beyrouth (Beirut, Lebanon); 1 Photographic Prints; 17.7 x 12.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Beirut, Lebanon; Hotels; Men; Women; Restaurants/bars; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Drinks/Beverages; Facial Hair
  - A portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian., Circa 1950-1970; ref774; Issa Freres, Beyrouth (Beirut, Lebanon); 1 Photographic Prints; 16.3 x 10.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Women; Hotels; Restaurants/bars; Beirut, Lebanon; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of three men and two women, Marie Rose Krikorian wears a fur coat next to Jareh Krikorian (right)., Circa 1950-1970; ref775; 1 Photographic Prints; 17 x 11 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Cairo, Egypt; Hotels; Restaurants/bars; Paintings; Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Drinks/Beverages; Fur Garments
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose and Jareh Krikorian dancing., Circa 1950-1970; ref776; 1 Photographic Prints; 16 x 10.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Dancing; Lebanon; Jewelry; Restaurants/bars; Hotels; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Gatherings
  - An envelope., 1974; ref777; 1 Photographic Prints; 13 x 10.6 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Damascus, Syria; French Writing; Postal Stamps; Cyprus; Printed Materials
  - A studio envelope from Studio Georges Derzi, Circa 1940-1970; ref778; Studio Georges Derzi, Press Photography Department, Salhieh, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 15.3 x 12.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; English Writing; Advertisements; Studio Photography; Printed Materials
  - A studio portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian., Circa 1940-1950; ref779; 1 Photographic Prints; 22.5 x 16.1 cm (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Women; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A studio portrait of Marie Rose and Jareh Krikorian., Circa 1940-1950; ref780; 1 Photographic Prints; 22.7 x 16.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Men; Women; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of three women and two men at a dinner table, including Marie Rose and Jareh Krikorian (right)., Circa 1950-1970; ref781; Sons et Couleurs (Beirut, Lebanon); 1 Photographic Prints; 16.3 x 11.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Casinos; Lebanon; Restaurants/bars; Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Drinks/Beverages
  - A portrait of a woman holding shoes at a shoe vendor (linked ref1079)., Circa 1960-1975; ref1076; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.9 x 11.6 cm (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Street Vendors; Fur Garments; Women; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of a teenage boy and girl dancing at the International Casino., August 1965; ref1077; 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 12.9 cm (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Dancing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria; Casinos; French Writing; Gatherings
  - A portrait of Jareh Krikorian speaking into a microphone (linked ref1103)., Circa 1960-1975; ref1078; 1 Photographic Prints; 19.8 x 12.2 cm (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Microphones; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A portrait of a woman holding shoes at a shoe vendor (linked ref1076)., Circa 1960-1975; ref1079; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.1 x 11.7 cm (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Women; Street Vendors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of a man shaking hands with a woman., Circa 1960-1975; ref1080; Studio Safar & Vartan, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 17.9 x 13.1 cm (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Men; Women; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria